ANS Record Group 3: Development and Membership
ANS Archives
ANS Record Group 3: Development and Membership
1866-ongoing
Development records, including those relating to fund raising; coin, library, and cash donations; annual and planned giving; bequests; endowment campaigns; and grant applications. Also, membership records such as those pertaining to meetings and events; correspondence on membership status; membership data; publicity materials such as press releases, circulars, and other promotional materials; and membership publications like the ANS Newsletter and Magazine, including photographs.
30 cubic feet
American Numismatic Society
PORTIONS OF THE FINDING AID ARE SUPPRESSED FROM PUBLIC VIEW. ANS staff can log into Staff View for the full record group description.
Parts of this finding aid, including descriptive notes and container lists, can only be viewed by logging in to Staff View.
Access
Portions are closed to outside researchers.
- Series: Membership card indexes and lists, 1858-1989; 1.5 cubic feet (16 boxes)
  Contains card indexes kept by the ANS as a record of each member, and can include such information as year joined, type of membership, collecting interests, home address, occupation, affiliations, and date of death. Some have additional attached biographical materials, such as obituaries and death notices. Though the information on the cards begin in 1858 when the Society was founded, the earliest cards, covering the years 1858 to 1925, appear to have been prepared retroactively as a set. The rest of the card record was begun sometime afterwards. The cards were used until about 1989 when the information was computerized. Also included are one set of cards that were filled out as applications for membership (1920s) and three bound volumes and one file of loose pages containing lists of members (1880s-1910s).
  Card indexes; Lists (Document genres); Notebooks
  Portions are closed to outside researchers.
  - Box 1 of 16: 1858-1925, A-N
  - Box 2 of 16: 1858-1925, O-Z
  - Box 3 of 16: Dropped, Abiuso-Juszko
  - Box 4 of 16: Dropped, Kabbaz-Voultsos
  - Box 5 of 16: Dropped, Wagner-Zyskind
  - Box 6 of 16: Resigned, Ainslow-Lynch
  - Box 7 of 16: Resigned, McGovern-Zug
  - Box 8 of 16: Superceded, A-Hyman
  - Box 9 of 16: Superceded, Indiana-Szego
  - Box 10 of 16: Superceded, Tabarroni-Wacks
  - Box 11 of 16: Deceased, Adams-Muzio
  - Box 12 of 16: Deceased, Nayville-Zygman
  - Box 13 of 16: Computerized 1989, Abecassis-Kushnet
  - Box 14 of 16: Computerized 1989, Kwiatkowski-Warrell
  - Box 15 of 16: Membership application cards, 1920s
  - Box 16 of 16: Three bound volumes and loose lists of members
- Series: General photographs, 1868-ongoing; 10 cubic feet (23 boxes)
  Photographs; Compact discs
  Open to outside researchers, but are subject to ANS policies on permission and fees for reproduction and use.
  Contains the prints, negatives, and, for some later years, compact discs of the American Numismatic Society’s general photograph collection, most of which, particularly in the later years, were produced for membership publications. The earliest items are member portraits on cartes de visite (1860s and 1870s) and cabinet cards (1870s-circa 1910). With few exceptions, these are the only original nineteenth-century images in this collection. The decades of the twentieth century up through the 1960s are represented by about 2 cubic feet of pictures on scattered topics, including portraits, numismatic events, exhibits, Medal of Honor recipients (1918-1919), and views of the Society’s Audubon Terrace headquarters, which include the construction of an addition to the building (1929-1930) and ANS exhibition rooms before and after remodeling (1945, 1950s). Beginning in the 1970s, the photographs are more numerous and more comprehensive, many produced for the Society’s newsletter, which began in 1979 and was succeeded by the ANS Magazine in 2002. These show staff, officers, members, students, and awardees at events such as the annual meeting, annual gala, lectures, exhibits, award ceremonies, Summer Seminar, and Coinage of the Americas (COAC) and other conferences. In addition, there are posed staff portraits and images relating to the Society’s move from its Audubon Terrace headquarters at 155th Street to Fulton Street in the late 1990s and early 2000s. Also included are copy negatives and page proofs for Howard L. Adelson’s book, The American Numismatic Society, 1858-1958 (1958), and undated photographs of coins, medals, and decorations.
  - Box 1 of 23: Early member portraits: cartes de viste, mostly 1860s-1870s
    Contents:
    [unidentified] (reverse: May 12, 1869; taken at Israel & Co., Baltimore); Ahlborn, Lea (front: Royal Mint Medal Engraver in Stockholm); Amelung, J.A.; Anthon, Charles Edward; Applegate, J. Henry; Appleton, William Sumner (reverse: Boston, dress worn in Syria); Baily, James Muhlenberg (reverse: died February 27, 1897); Barnard, Charles E. (reverse: Utica, N.Y.); Bolen, J.A. (two different photographs; reverse: Springfield, Mass.); Boucher, A.J. (reverse: Montreal); Bramhall, William Leggett (reverse: Washington, D.C.); Brock, Alonzo A.; Cauffman, Emil (reverse: Philadelphia); Clay, Charles; Clogston, William (reverse: Springfield, Mass.); Colburn, Jeremiah (reverse: Boston); Da Silva, B.; Davis, Robert C. (reverse: Philadelphia); De Peyster, J. Watts; Dubois, William E.; Ely, Herman; Engstrom, A.B. (reverse: from Arendal, Norway); Greenwood, Isaac J.; Groh, Edward; Groh, Henry; Gschwend, Charles; Hanna, John; Hewitt, Robert, Jr. (reverse: New York City); Hodgson, George; Idell, G.W.; James, Fred H. (reverse: Lancaster, N.Y.); Levick, Joseph Napoleon Tricot; Lightbody, Colin; Lionhardt, George G. (reverse: Augusta, Ga.); MacKenzie, Mortimer L.; McCoy, John F. (reverse: taken some five years ago, N.Y., February 17, 1868); Mickley, Joseph J.; Moore, Michael (reverse: Trenton Falls); Nichols, C. Porter (reverse: Springfield, Mass.); Ogden, R.W.; Oliver, James (two different photographs; reverse: to replace me in Society’s album); Parish, Jr., Daniel; Parker, Jas. (reverse: Springfield, Mass.); Perine, G.H.; Phillips, George L. (reverse: Dayton, Ohio); Prime, William C.; Ralston, J. Grier (reverse: Norristown, Pa.); Rivett, Nathaniel; Sage, Augustus B.; Sandham, Alfred; Stickney, Matthew Adams (reverse: Salem, Mass.); Taylor, A.B.; Taylor, James H.; Edward L. Tiemann (front: 1875)
  - Box 2 of 23: Early member portraits: cabinet cards, 1870s-circa 1910 (1 of 2)
    Adams, William; Ahlborny, Leu; Alphonse XIII, King of Spain (reverse: honorary member, 1910); Attinelli, Emmanuel Joseph; Balman, Henry L. (reverse: with compliments, April 11, 1890); Barnum, George Grenville (reverse: Buffalo, N.Y.); Belden, Bauman L. (reverse: January, 1897); Brenner, Victor David; Cogan, Edward; Cogan, George W. (front: youngest son of Edward at 17); Cohen (no first name given); Courteau, Eugene (reverse: 1903, aged 35); Cunningham, Thomas (reverse: Mohawk, N.Y.); Darling, C.W. (note: Utica); Dreier, Ludwig; Eklund, Ole P., (Two photographs, circa 1940s; reverse: long note mentioning age [66] and what is pictured, including his homestead in Idaho and a cabin he lived in (1889-1910) and a Mr. McKenzie, whose coins were sold “recently” by Stack’s); Elder, Thomas (picture postcard sent to Howland Wood, 1906; front: September 4, 1906); Ely, Foster (reverse: rector of St. Stephen’s Church, Ridgefield, Connecticut); Ford, [illegible]; Gregory, Charles (reverse: March 1889); Groh, Edward (reverse: 1883); Hall, [illegible] (photo taken in Nova Scotia); Harris, Robert; Harzfeld, Sigismund K. (reverse: 1877); Hickcox, John Howard; Higgins, Frank C. (reverse: September 5-10, 1910); Hills, J. Coolidge; Huberich, Charles H. (as a boy); Kirkwood, J.
  - Box 3 of 23: Early member portraits: cabinet cards, 1870s-circa 1910 (2 of 2)
    Lederer, Philipp (picture postcard, 1944?); Lee, William; Leverel, Herbert (reverse: member 1885); Lillardi, J.L.B. (front: 1894); Low, Lyman (reverse: June 2, 1888); Low, Lyman (reverse: 1891); Manuel II, King of Portugal (reign: 1908-1910); Massamore, George W. (front: Baltimore, July 10, 1886); Mitchelson, Joseph Chappel; Morgan, George T (low quality reprint; reverse: gift of Margo Russell, 1974; original photograph in the Bureau of the Mint Archives); Morris, Charles; Morris, Rob (engraved image on paper taken from an 1882 photograph); Parish, Daniel, Jr.; Perini, Quintilio (proceedings: Rovereto, Austria); Pfund, Anthony (reverse: photo compliments of Pfund, January 27, 1896; born June 12, 1823); Poillon, William; Saltus, John Sanford (reverse: 1895); Sandham, Alfred; Scott, John Walker (reverse: November 2, 1845 [his birth date]; September 1889); Sterling, E.B.; Stewart, William Rhinelander (reverse: 1893); Tuthill, Luther B. (note: May 29, 1894); Victor Emanuel III, King of Italy (honorary member, January 21, 1901); Wright, Charles Henry; Wyckoff, Peter B.; Zabrinske, Andrew C.
  - Box 4 of 23: Adelson
    Photographs for Howard L. Adelson’s book The American Numismatic Society, 1858-1958 (1958). About 50 4x5 copy negatives, mostly portraits of people copied from publications, some with corresponding prints; loose prints; and page proofs with photographic plates in place and labeled.
  - Box 5 of 23: Portraits, headquarter buildings, Audubon Terrace, Graduate Student Seminar, 1850s-1990s, Note: Was box 19.7.1.
    Includes negatives and copy prints, possibly for Adelson book, and some original photographs. Many portrait photographs are copies of ANS cartes de visite and copies from publications and other sources, including those of drawings and etchings. Box contains no nineteenth-century originals but a few from the early twentieth century.
    Portraits: Adams, Edward D.; Ahlborn, Lea; King of Spain Alphonse XIII; Anthon, Charles; Applegate, J. Henry; Appleton, William S., 1867-1903; Babelon, Ernst, 1910 (painting); Bailey, James Muhlenberg; Balog, Paul; Belden, Bauman; Bishoff, William L.; Bramhall, William L.; Brenner, Victor D., 1894-1924; Burnham, Roger, 1923; Chapman, H., 1935; Clapp, George, 1939; Cogan, Edward; Colburn, Jeremiah; Comparette, T. Louis; De Peyster, J. Watts; Dewing, Arthur S.; Dilliston (William H.?); Dodd, Charles; Douglas, Damon C., 1944, 1946; Drowne; Henry Russell; Dubois, W.M.E.; Duffield, Frank G.; Edlow, Kenneth; Eidlitz; English, Thomas Dunn; French, Daniel Chester; Greenwood, Isaac J.; Groh, Edward; Hanna, John; Havemeyer, Henry Osborne; Hewitt, Robert, Jr.; Hickox, John H.; Higgins, Frank H.; Huntington, Archer M. (includes Barcelona monument); Kunz, George F.; Lagerberg, Julius de, 1907; Lagerberg, Magnus Edward; Langdon, Woodburg; Levick, Joseph N.T.; Low, Lyman H.; Manship, Paul; King Manuel of Portugal; Mateu y Llopis, Felipe; Metcalf, William E.; Mickley, Joseph J.; Miles, George C., 1973; Newman, Eric; Norton, Frank; Norweb, R. Henry, Jr.; Oliver, James; Parish, Daniel, Jr.; Parmelee, Louis G.; Perine, George H.; Poillon, William; Pyne, Moses Taylor; Robertson, Robert; Roty, Louis-Oscar, 1889; St. Gaudens, Augustus; Sage, Augustus; Saltus, Sanford J.; Schiff, Jacob Henry; Simpson, A. Carson; Stewart, W.R.; Storer, Horatio R. (plaque); Thompson, Margaret; Turnure, Lawrence; Umberto; Vanderbilt, William Kissam; Vanderbilt, Conelius; King of Italy Victor Emanuel III; Weeks, William R.; West, Louis C.; Wood, Howland; Wormser, Moritz; Wright, Charles Henry; Wyman, Arthur C.; Zabriskie, Andrew; Zerbe, Farran.
    - New York Academy of Medicine
    - Union Dime Savings Bank
    - Cooper Union, October 20, 1859—Board of Education
    - 21st and 4th Ave.
    - New York University, Washington Square
    - Bible House and Cooper Institute—Chapter 2
    - Hispanic Society, pre 1905
    - Audubon Terrace, circa 1908
    - ANS exterior, circa 1908
    - ANS exterior—Etching, 1908
    - ANS interior—East Hall, 1908
    - ANS East Hall, 1908-1945
    - ANS exterior, 1915
    - ANS exterior—Construction of west wing, 1928-1930
    - ANS interior—West Hall, 1930
    - ANS exterior, 1928-1930
    - ANS exterior, post 1930
    - ANS interior—East Hall gallery, 1935
    - Audubon Terrace fence, 1950s
    - ANS East Hall, 1952
    - ANS interior, circa 1956
    - ANS East Hall—1201 series, circa 1957
    - ANS East and West Hall—2826 series, circa 1957
    - ANS Interior, circa 1990
    - Summer Seminar 1952
    - Summer Seminar 1984
    - Summer Seminar 1985
    - Summer Seminar 1986
    - Summer Seminar 1995
    - Summer Seminar 1996
    - Summer Seminar 1998
    - Summer Seminar 1999
    - Seminar—Various
    - ANS offices, people, computers—Some color, 1980s-1990s?
  - Box 6 of 23: 1870s-1989
    - Exhibit: Ancient Numismatics – Werner Gallery, University of Oregon, [year?]
    - Exhibit: Cleveland Museum, [year?]
    - Exhibit: Henry Chapman, [year?]
    - John Adams Bolen, late 1800s - Modern copy prints
    - Montroville Dickeson with Native American Indian – Modern copy print from Robert Wester in 1984, 1860s-1870s
    - Early Portraits – modern copy negatives – George and Ed Cogan, Lyman Low, John Walter Scott, J.K. Haryfeld, George W. Keafsamore, E.J. Attinelli 1870s-1890s
    - Charcoal portrait of an unidentified man, early 1900s?
    - United States Mint – New Orleans, early 1900s?
    - Howland Wood, early 1900s
    - Early Portraits – Hugo O. Greenhood, F.S. Duffield, Matthew A. Stickney, Lorin Parmelee, Francis ?, early 1900s
    - Early Portraits and other images – W.B.O. Field, Kurt Regling, George C. Hines, J. Hunt Deacon, Egerton Smith engraving, etc., early 1900s
    - Agnes Baldwin (Brett)?, early 1900s
    - Chief Thundercloud - Copies - Originals at the Rochester Numismatic Association, early 1900s
    - ANS building – Audubon Terrace – one view of exterior, early 1900s
    - New York Numismatic Club – Keen’s Chophouse negative, early 1900s
    - Thomas Elder banquet, early 1900s
    - New Theatre postcard, early 1900s
    - King ?, early 1900s
    - King of Italy - King Victor Emmanuel III, ca. 1901
    - King of Spain – Alphonso XIII, ca. 1905
    - Edgar H. Adams – Coney Island, 1905
    - Farran Zerbe, ca. 1906
    - Henry Chapman portraits, 1908 and later
    - King of Belgium – King Albert I, ca. 1910
    - King of Portugal – Manuel II, ca. 1910
    - ANA convention – from Elder Magazine, 1910
    - Audubon Terrace – Hispanic Society and ANS, 1913
    - Farran Zerbe – Money of the World exhibit – San Francisco, 1915
    - Medal of Honor recipients, including Civil War veterans, circa 1918-1919
    - Presentation to Prince of Wales, 1919
    - Portrait of an unidentified man, 1920s
    - Will Rogers – Misidentified as Arthur J. Fecht, 1926
    - Beach and harbor scenes, unidentified, 1930s?
    - Maximilian Bernhart – his profile on a plaque, 1930
    - Photographs taken at ANS by L.S. Werner – Edward Newell, Howland Wood, etc., 1935, 1943
    - Julio Berzunza – with his collection of Alexandriana books, 1940s?
    - Edward T. Newell plaque, 1940s
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Service (Ankara?) – Robert Kelly, General Tindal, Earle Parker, 1945
    - Insignia and Chevrons of the United States Marine Corps, mid-1900s?
    - ANS exhibition room before and after remodeling, 1945, 1950s
    - ANS exhibit at Exposition Spain, 1951
    - Traveling Exhibition – Coins of the Centuries, 1952
    - Archer M. Huntington Plaque, 1953 (plaque date)
    - George Miles, Sture Bolin, Kenneth Jenkins (in Stockholm, Sweden?), and Jean Babelon, Victor Tourneur, etc., in France, 1960s?
    - Stockholm, Sweden conference – Philip Grierson, George C. Miles, Humphrey Sutherland, August 1960
    - Nancy Waggoner with unidentified man, 1960s
    - World’s Fair exhibit, 1964
    - COINage photos for Larry Stevens article (vol. 5, no. 10, Oct. 1969), 1969
    - ANS – Coins of India exhibit, 1970s?
    - Florence Donnelly, Marie Martin, 1970s?
    - Harry Bass with unidentified man, 1970s?
    - Dexter Seymore, 1970s or 1980s
    - ANS library – Frank Campbell, 1970s
    - ANS – Margaret Thompson, Leslie Elam, etc., 1971
    - ANS – Annual meeting, Thodore V. Buttrey, Jr., Harald Ingholt, Jan. 13, 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), Sept. 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), Monday, Sept. 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), Monday Audubon Terrace, Sept. 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), Tuesday, Brooklyn, Sept. 1973
    - International Numismatic Congress (INC), Coinage of the Americas exhibit, 1973
    - ANS annual meeting, Jan. 1976
    - ANS annual meeting, World Coin News clipping, Feb. 1, 1977
    - Eric P. Newman, 1978
    - ANS event – Harry Bass, etc., April 8, 1978
    - ANS event – Harry Bass, etc., Dec. 8, 1978
    - Goetz medal exhibit – Mr. and Mrs. Ira Goldberg, Harry Fowler, Nancy Waggoner, etc., Dec. 8, 1978
    - William Metcalf and unidentified man, April 1979
    - ANA 50-year Medal, Henry Grunthal, 1979
    - ANS event – Harry Bass, etc., April 7, 1979
    - ANS exhibit hall, 1980s?
    - Various portraits – Arthur Houghton, Margo Russell, George Curth, John Kleeberg, etc., 1980s?
    - ANS event – Margaret Thompson, Richard Doty, William Metcalf, Nancy Waggoner, Alan Stahl, Rose Chan Houston, etc., 1980s?
    - ANS event – Margaret Thompson, 1980s?
    - ANS event – William Metcalf, Leslie Elam, etc., 1980s?
    - William Metcalf, 1980s?
    - Coin exhibits, 1980s?
    - ANS event – Elizabeth Jones, Harry Bass, Karen Worth, 1980s
    - Stack Family – 1980s
    - ANS miscellaneous – computers, library, Eric Newman teaching seminar, etc., 1980s
    - ANS miscellaneous – Michael Amandry, Elizabeth Jones, Karen Worth, 1980s
    - ANS event, April 1982
    - 1983 Los Angeles Olympic one dollar coin model and designer Elizabeth Jones, circa 1983
    - World of Coins exhibit – Audubon interiors, 1983
    - ANS 125th anniversary medal – Jovine’s rejected design, Jovine’s drawing of accepted design, 1983
    - ANS 125th anniversary, 1983
    - ANS group photo – Emery May Norweb, Frank Campbell, Chapman family, April 1983
    - ANS – Eric Newman, Harry Bass, etc.
    - ANS annual meeting – Margaret Thompson, 1984
    - ANS annual meeting – Karen Worth, etc., Jan. 14, 1984
    - ANS annual meeting – Karen Worth, Harry Bass, etc., Jan. 14, 1984
    - ANS spring meeting – Walter Breen, Harry Bass, Eric Newman, etc., April 14, 1984
    - ANS – John Kroll, Harry Bass, etc., Oct. 13, 1984
    - ANS annual meeting, 1985
    - ANS annual meeting – Marcel Jovine, Karen Worth, 1985
    - ANS - Saltus exhibit (Kauko Rasanen), historical costumes, Audubon exterior, fundraising flier, 1986
    - Exhibit: Money – Jorvick Viking Center, York, U.K., 1986
    - ANS T-shirt – Melqarejo, Richard Doty, Leslie Elam, April 1986
    - ANS event – Harry Fowler
    - ANS – William Metcalf, Frank Campbell, etc., Nov. 1986
    - ANS reception at World Trade Center, Jan. 9, 1987
    - Coinage of the Americas Conference (COAC), PR-BA COAC, Oct.-April, 1987
    - ANS event – Windows on the World, permanent exhibits, 1987
    - Development campaign launch reception, January 1987
    - Norweb dinner – Henry Fowler, Henry Norweb, 1987/1988?
    - ANS – Audubon Terrace exhibit hall and exteriors, 1988
    - ANS endowment drive dinner – silver medal awardees, John Kroll, Eric Newman, Harry Fowler, etc.
    - Coinage of the Americas Conference (COAC) – coin photos, 1988
    - ANS press release – Harry Bass, Walter Breen, Elizabeth Jones, etc., 1989?
    - Coinage of the Americas Conference (COAC) – coin photograph, 1989
  - Box 7 of 23: 1989-2002
    - John Kroll, Oct. 13, 1989
    - ANS miscellaneous – Alan Stahl, Richard Hoge, Richard Doty, etc., 1990s?
    - ANS miscellaneous events – 1990s
    - ANA event – Windows on the World, 1990s?
    - Coinage of the Americas Conference (COAC), 1990s?
    - ANS event – Bob Julian, John Wright, Steve Ellsworth, Eric Newman, Michael Bates, etc., 1990s?
    - ANS events – Eric Newman, R. Henry Norweb, Jr., etc., 1990s
    - Frank Deak – ANS photographer, 1990s
    - ANS event – Eric Newman, Elizabeth Jones, Harry Bass, Harry Fowler, striking anvil, 1990s
    - ANS event – Eric Newman, Harry Bass, Harry Fowler, vaulted interior, Robert Edlow tablet, 1990s
    - ANS event, 1990s
    - ANS staff photographs for holiday cards, 1990s
    - British Art Medal Society (BAMS)
    - Slides – vault, Frank Deak, Michael Bates, library, visitor area, Leslie Elam, Florence Donnelly, etc., 1990
    - Harry Fowler tribute, June 10, 1990
    - Color slides – Audubon building, library, medals, staff, etc., 1991
    - Roger A. Hornsby, Apr. 1991
    - Symposium on Mexican Coinage and Finance – Richard Doty, John Kleeberg, etc., Jan. 24 & 25, 1992
    - ANS – Princeton field trip, Jan. 23, 1993
    - Perspectives on the Renaissance Medal – June 4&5, 1994
    - Correspondence – Arlene Jacobs (development officer) to Lynnn Saville (photographer), 1995
    - ANS Gala – Eric Newman, Elena Stolyarik, circa 1996
    - Eric P. Newman dinner, Oct. 25, 1996
    - ANS – Miscellaneous photos received, Feb. 20, 1996
    - Coinage of the Americas Conference (COAC) – Negatives, fall 1997
    - ANS annual meeting – Negatives, winter 1998
    - Fowler lecture – Michael Amandry, etc., 1999
    - Saltus awards – Cedar Tavern, Feb. 13, 1999
    - Fulton Street building, 2000?
    - ANS event – early 2000s?
    - Coin Day – Fulton Street, June 5, 2000
    - Coin Day – Fulton Street, June 5, 2000
    - Delivery of 1933 Double Eagle to the Federal Reserve (?), 2002
  - Box 8 of 23: Late 1990s
    Mostly color prints and negatives, loose and in developers’ envelopes. Includes various events and Fulton building. Mostly late 1990s.
  - Box 9 of 23: 1977-1984
    ANS Newsletter and other negatives and contact prints, 1977-1984. Includes events, exhibits, Summer Seminar, Audubon Terrace interiors, computer systems, Bechtler coin press, Chapman exhibit (1983), weight machine, Margaret Thompson, and other topics.
  - Box 10 of 23: 1986-1989
    ANS Newsletter and other negatives and contact prints, 1986-1989.
  - Box 11 of 23: 1990-1993
  - Box 12 of 23: 1994-1997
    ANS Newsletter and other negatives and contact prints, 1994-1997.
  - Box 13 of 23: 1985-1992
    ANS Newsletter photographs, 1985-1992, with some newsletters.
  - Box 14 of 23: 1993-1999
    ANS Newsletter photographs, 1993-1999, with some newsletters.
  - Box 15 of 23: 2002
    David Tripp Double Eagle Lecture, Federal Reserve, June 20, 2002 (One set of 4x6 color prints)
  - Box 16 of 23: 2003
    Includes color 3x5 prints with 35 millimeter negatives.
    - “1933” opening
    - Bass Luncheon, opening of the Harry W. Bass Jr. Library, February 2003
    - 2003 Annual Meeting, October 2003
    - “Full Circle” Olympic opening
    - Federal Reserve “Gold Hoard from Israel” January 14, 2003
  - Box 17 of 23: 2004
    - ANS Ford dedication (with compact disc), May 13, 2004
    - Williams Street dedication (with compact disc), June 18, 2004
    - Huntington Award (portfolio with compact disc), October 22, 2004
    - Annual Meeting (portfolio with compact disc), October 23, 2004
    - David Tripp Lecture (portfolio with compact disc), November 10, 2004
    - Borglum Sculpture Removal (portfolio with compact disc), December 5, 2004
    - COAC 2004
    - Gala 2004, Plaza Hotel, in honor of Ken Edlow
  - Box 18 of 23: 2005-2007
    - Sale of Broadway, 155th St. (sheet with color thumbnails and compact disc), May 11, 2005
    - New York on Steel Opening, photos by Rosemary Lazenby (2 compact discs), February 8, 2005
    - Gala & Auction 2005 (portfolio with compact disc), Plaza Hotel, January 13, 2005
    - Sanford Saltus Award (portfolio with compact disc), September 17, 2005
    - Annual Meeting (portfolio with compact disc), October 22, 2005